Guide to the Paul Revere Reynolds Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Paul Revere Reynolds Papers
1899-1980.
Reynolds, Paul Revere, 1864-1944.
117 linear ft. (269 boxes)
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New York, NY.
Ms#1065
4079583
Historical Note
Paul Revere Reynolds became the first literary agent in America when he established his business in New York in 1893. Together with is son, Paul Revere Reynolds, Jr. (1904- ), he handled some of the most prominent British and American authors of the late nineteenth and early twentieth century. The son joined his father in 1923 and later became president of the agency.
Scope and Content
Papers of Paul Revere Reynolds and his son, Paul Revere Reynolds, Jr., consisting of correspondence, contracts, scripts, and financial records. The files are rich in correspondence between authors and agents and provide important information about some of the most significant works published in the last seventy years.
Arrangement
Material arranged into three series:
Series I: Cataloged Correspondence
Series II: Uncataloged Correspondence
Series III: Financial Records
Subjects
Allingham, Margery, 1904-1966.; Alsop, Joseph, 1910-1989.; Asquith, H. H. (Herbert Henry), 1852-1928.; Auchincloss, Louis.; Bangs, John Kendrick, 1862-1922.; Beer, Thomas.; Benchley, Robert, 1889-1945.; Bennett, Arnold, 1867-1931.; Bolton, Guy, 1884-1979.; Bridges, Robert, 1858-1941.; Burnett, Whit, 1899-1973.; Bynner, Witter, 1881-1968.; Caldwell, Erskine, 1903-1987.; Cather, Willa, 1873-1947.; Churchill, Winston, 1871-1947.; Churchill, Winston, 1874-1965.; Costain, Thomas B. (Thomas Bertram), 1885-1965.; Cousins, Norman.; Doyle, Arthur Conan, Sir, 1859-1930.; Dreiser, Theodore, 1871-1945.; Dunbar, Paul Laurence, 1872-1906.; Edel, Leon, 1907-1997.; Ellis, Havelock, 1859-1939.; Fast, Howard, 1914-2003.; Ferber, Edna, 1887-1968.; Fisher, Dorothy Canfield, 1879-1958.; Galsworthy, John, 1867-1933.; Gardner, Erle Stanley, 1889-1970.; Glasgow, Ellen Anderson Gholson, 1873-1945.; Goldberg, Rube, 1883-1970.; Harris, Frank, 1855-1931.; Harris, Joel Chandler, 1848-1908.; Hassall, Christopher, 1912-1963.; Hillary, Edmund, 1919-2008.; Howells, William Dean, 1837-1920.; Hurst, Fannie, 1889-1968.; Huxley, Aldous, 1894-1963.; Keppel, Frederick P. (Frederick Paul), 1875-1943.; Kreymborg, Alfred, 1883-1966.; Lang, Andrew, 1844-1912.; Leary, Timothy, 1920-1996.; London, Jack, 1876-1916.; Loveman, Amy.; McLuhan, Marshall, 1911-1980.; Mailer, Norman.; X, Malcolm, 1925-1965.; Masefield, John, 1878-1967.; Masters, Edgar Lee, 1868-1950.; Maugham, W. Somerset (William Somerset), 1874-1965.; Middleton, Drew, 1913-1990.; Moore, George, 1852-1933.; Nash, Ogden, 1902-1971.; Norris, Frank, 1870-1902.; Post, Emily, 1873-1960.; Putnam, George Palmer, 1887-1950.; Rohmer, Sax, 1883-1959.; Richter, Conrad, 1890-1968.; Searle, Ronald, 1920-; Shaw, Bernard, 1856-1950.; Sinclair, Upton, 1878-1968.; Steffens, Lincoln, 1866-1936.; Stegner, Wallace Earle, 1909-1993.; Strachey, Lytton, 1880-1932.; Suckow, Ruth, 1892-1960.; Tarkington, Booth, 1869-1946.; Thomas, Lowell, 1892-1981.; Trench, Herbert, 1865-1923.; Tyler, Parker.; Untermeyer, Louis, 1885-1977.; Vonnegut, Kurt.; Wallace, Irving, 1916-1990.; Webb, Beatrice, 1858-1943.; Webb, Sidney, 1859-1947.; Wells, H. G. (Herbert George), 1866-1946.; Wheelock, John Hall, 1886-1978.; Wilder, Thornton, 1897-1975.; Wodehouse, P. G. (Pelham Grenville), 1881-1975.; Zangwill, Israel, 1864-1926.; Authors.; Authors and publishers.; Book proposals.; Copyright.; Literature publishing.; Account books.; Contracts.; Financial records.; Scripts.; Authors.; Literary agents.; Novelists.
Acquisition
Records Reynolds, Paul Revere, Jr. & Robin Reynolds Gift
Alternate Formats
Willa Cather letters are on microfilm.
Gift of Paul R. Reynolds, Jr., 1972, 1982 & 1984.
Gift of Robbin Reynolds, 1988.
- Series I: Cataloged Correspondence
  Cataloged Correspondence is stored onsite in the Rare Book & Manuscript Library and can be requested in the library by the name of the correspondents
  - Allingham, Margery
  - Alsop, Joseph
  - Andrews, Mary Raymond Shipman
  - Asquith, Herbert: Henry, 1st Earl of Oxford and Asquith
  - Asquith, Margot Tennant, Countess of Oxford
  - Atherton, Gertrude Franklin Horn
  - Auchincloss, Louis Stanton
  - Baker, George Barr
  - Bangs, John Kendrick
  - Beach, Rex Ellingvood
  - Behrman, Samuel Nathaniel
  - Beer, Thomas
  - Benchley, Robert
  - Bennett, Arnold
  - Bolton, Guy
  - Bottomley, Gordon
  - Bridges, Robert (1858-1941)
  - Brooke, Emma Frances
  - Brown, Alice
  - Bryce, Lloyd
  - Burke Thomas
  - Burnett, Frances Hodgson
  - Burnett, Whit
  - Butler, Ellis Barker
  - Bynner, Witter
  - Cabell, James Branch
  - Caldwell, Erskine
  - Carman, Bliss
  - Castle, Egerton
  - Castle, Irene Foote (Mrs. Vernon)
  - Cather, Willa Silbert
    (on microfilm)
  - Catlin, Sir George Edward Gordon
  - Churchill, Winston (l871-1947)
  - Churchill, Sir Winston Leonard Spencer (1874-1965)
  - Cobb, Irvin Shrewsbury
  - Colby, Bainbridge
  - Costain, Thomas Bertram
  - Corbett, Elizabeth
  - Cousins, Norman
  - Croker, Bithia Mary Sheppard
  - Darrow, Whitney
  - Dashiell, Alfred Sheppard
  - Davis, Rebecca Blaine Harding
  - Davis, Richard Harding
  - Deibler, Frederick S.
  - Deland, Margaret Ware
  - De la Roche, Mazo
  - Dewey, Davis Rich
  - Dickson, Harris
  - Dmitri Pavlovich, Grand Duke of Russia
  - Douglas, E.L.
  - Doyle, Sir Arthur Conan
  - Dreiser, Theodore
  - Dunbar, Paul Laurence
  - Edel, Leon
  - Ellis, Havelock
  - Ellis, Mary Edith Mary Lees
  - Evans, Florence Wilkerson
  - Fairlie, John Archibald
  - Farley, Walter
  - Fast, Howard
  - Ferber, Edna
  - Field, James Alfred
  - Finley, John Huston
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield
  - Fiske, Amos Kidder
  - Flagg, James Montgomery
  - Forman, Justus Miles
  - Frohman, Daniel
  - Fyleman, Rose
  - Gale, Zona
  - Galsworthy, John
  - Galton, Frank Wallis
  - Gardner, Erie Stanley
  - Garland, Hamlin
  - Garnier, Russell Montague
  - Gibbs, Sir Philip
  - Gibson, Charles
  - Glasgow, Ellen
  - Grant, Robert
  - Goldberg, Rube
  - Green, Paul
  - Greener, William Oliver
  - Hagood, Johnson
  - Hamilton, Cosmo
  - Harris, Frank
  - Harris, Joel Chandler
  - Hassall, Christopher
  - Hayward, John
  - Herford, Oliver
  - Hillary, Sir Edmund
  - Holland, Vyvyan Beresford
  - Horgan, Paul
  - Howells, William Dean
  - Hurst, Fannie
  - Hutten zum Stolzenberg, Bettina Riddle, Baroness von
  - Huxley, Aldous
  - Huxley, Elspeth Josceline Grant
  - Jackson, Gabrielle Emilie Snow
  - James, Dorothea Draper Blagden (Mrs Henry)
  - Johnston, Mary
  - Kantor, MacKinlay
  - Kennerley, Mitchell
  - Keppel, Frederick Paul
  - Kreymbord, Alfred
  - Kubinyi, Victor von
  - Lande, Louis
  - Lang, Andrew
  - Leach, Henry Goddard
  - Leacock, Stephen
  - Leary, Timothy
  - Lincoln, Joseph "Crosby
  - Liveing, Edward George Downing
  - Locke, William John
  - Lodge, Sir Oliver
  - London, Jack
  - Loveman, Amy
  - MacKaye, Percy Wallace
  - McLuhan, Marshall
  - Mahan, Alfred Thayer
  - Mailer, Norman
  - Malcolm X
  - Mdasefield, John
  - Mathers, Helen
  - Masters, Edgar Lee
  - Maugham, William Somerset
  - Merrick, Leonard
  - Middleton, Drew
  - Millard, Christopher S.
  - Millis, Harry Alvin
  - Moffett, Cleveland
  - Moon, Parker Thomas
  - Moore, George
  - Moulton, Harold Glenn
  - Murray, Sir John
  - Mussey, Henry Raymond
  - Nash, Ogden
  - Norris, Frank
  - Osbourne, Lloyd
  - Oursler, Fulton
  - Moses, Robert
  - Page, Thomas Nelson
  - Page, Walter Hines
  - Peary, Robert Edwin
  - Perkins, Maxwell Evarts
  - Poole, Ernest
  - Porter, Gene Stratton
  - Post, Emily Price
  - Putnam, George Palmer
  - Rohmer, Sax
  - Richter, Conrad
  - Roosevelt, Kermit
  - Ross Williamson, Hugh
  - Ruck, Berta
  - Sadleir, Michael
  - Searle, Ronald
  - Sedgwick, Ellery
  - Shabazz, Betty
  - Shaw, George Bernard
  - Sinclair, Upton
  - Sorensen, Theodore C.
  - Steel, Flora Annie
  - Steelem Wilbur Daniel
  - Steffens, Lincoln
  - Stegner, Wallace
  - Strachey, Lionel
  - Strachey, Lytton
  - Suckow, Ruth
  - Sukhotin, Tatiana Tolstoy (Mrs Mikhail)
  - Sullivan, Mark
  - Sutro, Alfred
  - Tarbell, Ida Minerva
  - Tarkington, Booth
  - Tarkington, John S.
  - Tarkington, Laurel Louisa Fletcher (Mrs Booth)
  - Tarkington, Susannah Robinson (Mrs Booth)
  - Thaw, Harry Kendall
  - Towne, Charles Hanson
  - Thomas, Lowell
  - Tyler, Parker
  - Trench, Herbert
  - Untermeyer, Louis
  - Verne, Jules
  - Vonnegut, Kurt, Jr.
  - Wallace, Irving
  - Webb, Beatrice Potter (Mrs Sidney)
  - Webb, Sidney James
  - Wells, Amy Catherine Robbins (Mrs Herbert G.)
  - Wells, Herbert George
  - Wheelock, John Hall
  - White, Katherine Sergeant Angell (Mrs E.B.)
  - White, Stewart Edward
  - Wiggin, Kate Douglas
  - Wilder, Thornton
  - Wodehouse, Sir Pelham Grenville
  - Wodehouse, Ethel Rowley Wayman (Lady)
  - Zangwill, Israel
- Series II: Uncataloged Correspondence
  Uncataloged Correspondence is shelved off-site and should be requested by box number.
  - A -misc. (Box 1)
  - Abel, Elie (Box 1)
  - Adams, Clifton H. (Box 1)
  - Adams, Mildred (Box 201)
  - Adams, Gerald D. (Box 1)
  - Ainsworth, Louise (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Holmes (Box 1)
  - Allan, Alfred K. (Box 1)
  - Allan, Mabel Esther (Box 2)
  - Allan, Richard (Box 2)
  - Allen, Agnes Rogers (Box 3)
  - Allen, Anne (Box 3)
  - Allen, Charlotte Vale "Charles Valentine" (Box 3)
  - Allen, George N. (Box 3)
  - Allen, Thomas B. (Box 3)
  - Allingham, Margery Louise and Philip Youngman Carter (Box 3)
  - Allingham, Margery Louise (Box 201)
  - Allingham, Margery Louise and Philip Youngman Carter (Box 4)
  - American Heritage (Box 4)
  - American Heritage Press (Box 201)
  - Amifitheatrof, Erik (Box 4)
  - Amos, Ron (Box 4)
  - Amoury, Gloria (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Duncan M. (Box 201)
  - Anderson, John R.L. (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Richard L. (Box 4)
  - Andrews, Lewis M. (Box 4)
  - Anthony, Edward (Box 5)
  - Aplin, Jim (Box 201)
  - Armah, Ayi Kwei (Box 5)
  - Armour, Richard (Box 5)
  - Armour, Richard (Box 201)
  - Armour, Richard (Box 6)
  - Armour, Richard (Box 7)
  - Arnold, Margot (Petronelle M.M. Cook) (Box 7)
  - Ascher, Sheila and Dennis and Straus (Box 201)
  - Aske, Stephen, Literary Agent (Box 7)
  - Atheneum Publishers (Box 7)
  - Atkinson, Brian (Box 7)
  - The Atlantic Monthly (Box 7)
  - Atwood, Cole (Box 7)
  - Auerbach, Arnold "Red" and Paul Sann (Box 8)
  - Auerbach, Sylyia (Box 8)
  - Australia (Box 8)
  - The Authors Guild, Inc. (Box 201)
  - Author's Guidance Service (Box 8)
  - The Authors Guild, Inc./The Authors League of America (Box 8)
  - Ayeroff, Fred (Box 201)
  - Aylesworth, Virginia L (Box 8)
  - Ayrault, Evelyn West (Box 8)
  - B - misc. (Box 201)
  - B - misc. (Box 9)
  - Baber, Asa (Box 9)
  - Baber, Asa (Box 201)
  - Bailey, George (Box 10)
  - Bailey, George (Box 201)
  - Bailey, Ronald H. (Box 10)
  - Baird, Irene (Box 10)
  - Baker, George R.F. (Box 201)
  - Baker, Marceil G. and A.A. Baker "Marc Baker," "Marc Miller," "Marcia Miller" (Box 10)
  - Baker, Mary Lee (Box 10)
  - Baker, Robb (Box 10)
  - Baldwin, Anne Norris (Box 10)
  - Baldwin, Anne Norris (Box 201)
  - Baldwin, Gordon C. (Box 10)
  - Baldwin, Gordon C. (Box 11)
  - Ballantine, Bill (Box 11)
  - Ballantine, Bill (Box 201)
  - Ballantine, David (Box 11)
  - Banks, Polan (Box 11)
  - Barbeau, Clayton C. (Box 11)
  - Barber, Walter L. "Red" (Box 11)
  - Barber, Walter L. "Red" (Box 12)
  - Barber, Walter L. "Red" (Box 202)
  - Barker, Albert W. "Reefe King" (Box 12)
  - Barker, Albert W. "Reefe King" (Box 202)
  - Barker Ltd, Arthur (Box 12)
  - Barlett, Donald L. and James B. Steele (Box 12)
  - Barnes, Peter (Box 12)
  - Barstow, Stan (Box 202)
  - Bart/Levy Associates, Inc. (Box 12)
  - Barthold, James (Box 12)
  - Bartlett, Richard A. (Box 12)
  - Bass, George F. (Box 12)
  - Bassett, Sara Ware (Box 12)
  - Bassett, Sara Ware (Box 202)
  - Battelle, Phyllis (Box 12)
  - Bauer, Erwln A. (Box 12)
  - Bean, Amelia (Box 12)
  - Beardsley, Charles "Owen Elliott", "Jocelyn Radcliffe" (Box 12)
  - Beardsley, Charles "Owen Elliott", "Jocelyn Radcliffe" (Box 202)
  - Beazley, Hamilton, Jr. (Box 12)
  - Beck, Aaron T. (Box 12)
  - Becker, Robert 0. (Box 202)
  - Becker, Stephen (Box 12)
  - Beer, Thomas (Box 12)
  - Bell, J. Bowyer (Box 202)
  - Bell, J. Bowyer (Box 13)
  - Bellairs, John (Box 13)
  - Benchley, Robert (Box 13)
  - Bendiner, Alfred (Box 13)
  - Benedict, Helen (Box 202)
  - Bennett, Jack B (Box 202)
  - Bennett, Marcia J. (Box 202)
  - Bennett, M.J. (Box 13)
  - Bennington College (Box 202)
  - Benson, Ben (Box 13)
  - Benson, Mary (Box 13)
  - Benson, Mary (Box 202)
  - Bentley, John (Box 13)
  - Bergman, Jules (Box 13)
  - Berkus, Clara W. (Box 202)
  - Berns, Hendrik J. (Box 13)
  - Berman, Claire Gallant (Box 202)
  - Bernstein, Jeremy (Box 202)
  - Betancourt, Romulo (Box 14)
  - Bhattacharya, Bhabani (Box 14)
  - Bickham, Jack M. "Jeff Clinton" (Box 14)
  - Bickham, Jack M. (Box 15)
  - Birch, Alison Wyrley (Box 15)
  - Black, Ann McMurry (Box 15)
  - Black, Campbell (Box 15)
  - Black, James Cunard (Box 15)
  - Blackburn, John (Box 15)
  - Blackman, Carol (Box 15)
  - Blankfort, Michael (Box 15)
  - Black, Campbell (Box 16)
  - Black, James Cunard (Box 16)
  - Blackburn, John (Box 16)
  - Blackman, Carol (Box 16)
  - Blais, Madeleine (Box 203)
  - Blankfort, Michael (Box 16)
  - Bluestone, Naomi (Box 203)
  - Bluhmberg, Stanley A. (Box 203)
  - Boatner, Mary Mayo III (Box 203)
  - Bohle Edgar (Box 203)
  - Bohle, Edgar (Box 17)
  - Boles, Robert (Box 17)
  - Bolin, Luis A. (Box 17)
  - Bond, Nelson (Box 17)
  - Bonfante, Jordan (Box 17)
  - Bonime, Florence (Box 17)
  - Bonime, Florence (Box 203)
  - Booth Edwin (Box 203)
  - Booth, Edwin (Box 17)
  - Bottomley, Gordon (Box 17)
  - Bornstein, Dorothy (Box 17)
  - Bowen, Ezra (Box 17)
  - Bowen, Ezra (Box 203)
  - Bowen, Joshua David (Box 17)
  - Bowne, Ezra (Box 203)
  - Boyce, Burke (Box 17)
  - Boyd, Daniel Lamont (Box 17)
  - Boyd, Margaret A. (Box 17)
  - Brackman, Arnold C. (Box 18)
  - Braddon, Russell (Box 18)
  - Bradford, Amory H. (Box 18)
  - Brady, Timothy (Box 203)
  - Braider, Carol N. (Mrs Donald) (Box 18)
  - Braider, Donald (Box 19)
  - Braider, Donald (Box 20)
  - Bravermen, Katherine (Box 20)
  - Bramnick, Lea S. (Box 203)
  - Brandt, Anthony (Box 203)
  - Braverman, Katherine (Box 203)
  - Brawley, Ernest (Box 203)
  - Braynard, Frank O. (Box 20)
  - Brent, Harrison and Ruth H. (Box 20)
  - Brinig, Myron (Box 20)
  - Briskin, Jacqueline (Box 203)
  - Bristol, David P. (Box 203)
  - Brock, Stanley E. (Box 204)
  - Brock, Stanley E. (Box 20)
  - Brockway, George P. (Box 204)
  - Brodie, Bernard (Box 204)
  - Brody, Alan and Paula (Box 20)
  - Brookhouse, Christopher (Box 20)
  - Brookhouse, Christopher (Box 204)
  - Brooks, Bruce (Box 204)
  - Brooks, Lester and Patricia K. (Box 204)
  - Brown, Allen (Box 21)
  - Brown, Anthony Cave (Box 21)
  - Brown, Cecil (Box 21)
  - Brown, James William (Box 204)
  - Brown, Kenneth Calhoun (Box 21)
  - Brown, Mark H. (Box 204)
  - Brown, Mark H. and W.R. Felton (Box 21)
  - Brown, Peter (Box 204)
  - Brunner, John (Box 22)
  - Brunner, John (Box 205)
  - Brunner, John (Box 23)
  - Brussel, James A. and Theodore Irwin (Box 23)
  - Bryant, Beth (Box 24)
  - Bryant, Will (Box 24)
  - Buchanan, Henry A. (Box 24)
  - Buck, Robert N. (Box 24)
  - Burchardt, Bill "E.V. DuBois" (Box 24)
  - Burchardt, Hank (Box 205)
  - Burgess, Robert F. (Box 205)
  - Burgess, Robert F. (Box 24)
  - Burk, Gay (Box 24)
  - Burke, Alan Dennia (Box 205)
  - Burke, Thomas (Box 25)
  - Burke, Timmie (Box 25)
  - Burland, Brian Berkeley (Box 205)
  - Burn, Henry Pelham (Box 25)
  - Burnett, Frances Eliza Hodgson (Box 25)
  - Burns, Walter T. (Box 25)
  - Burroway, Janet (Box 205)
  - Burten, William S. (Box 205)
  - Burton, Edward J. "Michael Carey" (Box 25)
  - Busch, Frederick (Box 25)
  - Busnar, Gene (Box 205)
  - Butler, Gene (Box 205)
  - Butler, Gwendolyn "Jennie Melville" (Box 205)
  - Butler, Gwendolyn "Jennie Melville" (Box 25)
  - Butler, Samuel (Box 205)
  - Butt, Richard V. (Box 205)
  - Buttenwieser, Paul A. (Box 205)
  - Butterworth, William E. (Box 25)
  - Butterworth, William E. (Box 26)
  - Butwin, David (Box 26)
  - Byers, Bruce (Box 26)
  - C - misc. (Box 27)
  - C- misc (Box 206)
  - Caldwell, Erskine (Box 206)
  - Caldwell, William Vernon (Box 206)
  - Caldwell, William V. (Box 27)
  - Calkins, Frank James "C.Calkins" and Rodello Hunter (Box 27)
  - Campanella,-Roy (Box 28)
  - Campbell, Louise (Box 206)
  - Campbell, Stuart (Box 206)
  - Campbell, Walter Stanley (Box 28)
  - Cannon, Poppy (Mrs Walter White) (Box 28)
  - Cannon, Poppy (Box 206)
  - Cape Limited, Jonathan (Publishers) (Box 206)
  - Cape Cod Writers Conference (Box 206)
  - Capps, Benjamin (Box 28)
  - Carben, Edward (Box 28)
  - Carben, Edward (Box 206)
  - Carse, Robert (Box 206)
  - Carse, Robert (Box 29)
  - Carter, Mary (Box 29)
  - Carter, Samuel, III (Box 30)
  - Carter, Tom (Box 30)
  - Casewit, Curtis W. (Box 206)
  - Cashman, David (Box 206)
  - Cassini, Igor (Box 30)
  - Cater, Elizabeth (Box 30)
  - Cather, Willa Sibert (Box 30)
  - Cenedella, Robert (Box 206)
  - Chacko, Dacid (Box 206)
  - Chang, Kuo-sin (Box 30)
  - Chaplin, James P. (Box 30)
  - Chaplim, Patrice (Box 206)
  - Chapman, Colin (Box 206)
  - Charlottesville Conference (Box 206)
  - Chelminski, Rudolph (Box 206)
  - Chelminski, Rudolph (Box 30)
  - Chester, William L. (Box 31)
  - Chichester, Sir Francis (Box 31)
  - Chidsey, Donald Barr (Box 31)
  - Chidsey, Donald Barr (Box 32)
  - Chidsey, Donald Barr (Box 33)
  - Chidsey, Donald Barr (Box 206)
  - Childs, Henry C. (Box 206)
  - Chilton Book Company (Box 33)
  - Chinn, Laurene (Box 33)
  - Chinnock, Frank W. (Box 33)
  - Choate, Ernest A. (Box 206)
  - Choate, Gwen (Box 33)
  - Christian, Linda (Blanca Rosa Welter) (Box 33)
  - Cioffari, Philip (Box 33)
  - Clagett, John (Box 33)
  - Clagett, John (Box 206)
  - Clark, Geoffrey (Box 206)
  - Clarke, Loren K. (Box 206)
  - Clarke, Tom (Box 33)
  - Clay, Catherine Lee (Box 33)
  - Clayotn, John (Box 207)
  - Clearman, Mary (Box 34)
  - Cleary, John (Box 207)
  - Cleary, Jon Stephen (Box 207)
  - Cleary, Jon (Box 34)
  - Cleary, Jon (Box 35)
  - Cleaver, William and Vera (Box 35)
  - Clement, Ernest C. (Box 207)
  - Clement, Patricia W. (Box 207)
  - Cline, Lou Dean (L.D. Jacobs) (Box 35)
  - Cobb, Jocelyn (Box 207)
  - Cockrell, Marian (Box 207)
  - Cockrell, Marian (Box 35)
  - Coffin, Judy (Box 207)
  - Cohen, Helen (Box 35)
  - Cohen, Leah (Box 207)
  - Cohen, Stanley (Box 207)
  - Cohen, Stanley (Box 35)
  - Collier, Shirley, Agency (Box 35)
  - Collier, Shirley, Agency (Box 207)
  - Collins, V. Lansing (Box 35)
  - Colt, Ethel Barrymore (Box 36)
  - Columbia University. Writing Division. (Box 207)
  - Connelly, Thomas Lavrence (Box 36)
  - Connett, Bartan L. (Box 208)
  - Connolly, Edvard James (Box 36)
  - Conover, David (Box 36)
  - Constant, Nick (Box 36)
  - Conway, Eugene (Box 36)
  - Cook, Hilda (Box 36)
  - Cooke, Crispin (Box 36)
  - Cookridge, Edvard H. (Box 36)
  - Coolidge, Joseph (Box 36)
  - Cooper, Frank, Associates Agency, Inc./ FCA Agency, Inc. (Box 36)
  - Cooper, Joseph (Box 36)
  - Coover, Robert (Box 208)
  - Corning, Peter A. and Constance Hellyer Corning (Box 208)
  - Corning, Peter A. (Box 36)
  - Costello, John and Terry Hughes (Box 36)
  - Coward, Tom Wheaton (Box 36)
  - Cowles Communicationa, Inc. (Box 36)
  - Cox, William R. "Joel Reeve" (Box 36)
  - Craig, M. Jean (Box 208)
  - Craig, M. (Box 37)
  - Cranford, Peter G. (Box 37)
  - Crawford, Max (Box 208)
  - Creative Artists Agency, Inc. (Box 208)
  - Crews, Harry (Box 208)
  - Criterion Books, Inc. (Box 37)
  - Cronley, Jay (Box 208)
  - Crotty, Robert (Box 37)
  - Crowell, Robert L. (Box 37)
  - Crowell, Thomas Y., Company (Box 37)
  - Crown Publishers, Inc. (Box 37)
  - Cullinan, Elizabeth and Stephen Clark (Box 208)
  - Culp, John H. (Box 37)
  - Cumbie, Wylie (Box 37)
  - Cuningham, Michael (Box 208)
  - Cunnington, Vivian (Box 208)
  - Curtis, Greg (Box 208)
  - Curtis, Olga (Box 208)
  - Cutler, Ann (Box 208)
  - Cutler, John Henry (Box 37)
  - D - misc. (Box 37)
  - D - misc. (Box 209)
  - Dalbey, E. Gordon, Jr. (Box 209)
  - Dallas, Pat V. (Box 38)
  - Dalmas, Herbert (Box 38)
  - Dalmas, Herbert (Box 209)
  - Dalton, Robin, Associates (Box 38)
  - Damerell, Reginald G. (Box 38)
  - Dammann, Tom (Box 38)
  - Danze, Philip (Box 38)
  - Daves, Mrs. Delmer and Michael (Box 209)
  - Davies, A. Mervyn (Box 209)
  - Davis, Elise Miller (Box 209)
  - Davis, Elise Miller (Box 38)
  - Davis, Hope Hale (Box 38)
  - Davis, John A. (Box 209)
  - Davis, Judith L. "Judith Toral" (Box 209)
  - Davis Kenneth S. (Box 209)
  - Davis, Kenneth S. (Box 38)
  - Davis, Kenneth S. (Box 39)
  - Davis, Lou Ellen (Box 39)
  - Davis, William E. (Box 209)
  - Daws, Gavan "Allen Haydon" (Box 209)
  - Daws, Gavan "Allen Haydon" (Box 39)
  - Day, A. Grove (Box 40)
  - Day, A. Grove (Box 209)
  - Day, Beth (Box 209)
  - Day, Beth (Box 40)
  - Day Company Inc. Publishers, The John (Box 40)
  - Deal, Bordon and Babs (Box 41)
  - DeCicco, Alfred (Box 42)
  - DeCicco, Alfred (Box 210)
  - de Groot, Roy Andries (Box 42)
  - Dejeans, Elizabeth (Box 43)
  - de Kerpely, Theresa (Box 43)
  - de Kerpely, Theresa (Box 210)
  - Delbanco, Elena "Carter Greenhouse" (Box 210)
  - Delbanco, Nicholas (Box 210)
  - Delbanco, Nicholas (Box 44)
  - Dellums, Ronald V. (Box 44)
  - Depret, Didier (Box 44)
  - Detzer, David (Box 44)
  - Deutsch, Andre, Ltd (Box 44)
  - Devine, Laurie (Box 210)
  - Dew, Robb Forman (Box 210)
  - de Wiess, Ferdinand A. (Box 44)
  - Dewlen, Al (Box 44)
  - Dewlen, Al (Box 45)
  - The Dial Press (Box 46)
  - Dickey, Ralph (Box 210)
  - Dinkins, Stephanie (Box 210)
  - Dinkins, Stephanie (Box 46)
  - Dixon, Kent H. (Box 46)
  - Dobler, Bruce (Box 210)
  - Dobler, Bruce (Box 46)
  - Dodson, Reynolds (Box 46)
  - Doner, Mary Frances (Box 46)
  - Donovan, Frank R. (Box 46)
  - Donovan, Frank R. (Box 210)
  - Donovan, Maria (Box 46)
  - Dotto, Lydia (Box 46)
  - Doubleday (Box 47)
  - Douglas, Jack (Box 47)
  - Douglas, Jack (Box 210)
  - Dowdy, Andrew H. (Box 47)
  - Dowell, Dorothy (Box 210)
  - Downey, Fairfax (Box 48)
  - Downey, Fairfax (Box 48, Folder 49)
  - Downing, Warwick, II "John Paul Phillips (Box 50)
  - Doyle, Peter K. (Box 50)
  - Drake, Christine, S. (Box 210)
  - The Dramatists Guild, Inc. (Box 50)
  - Draper, Tom (Box 210)
  - Dromgoole, Richard H. (Box 50)
  - DuBois, Theodora (Box 211)
  - Dudley, Ernest "Ernest Coltman" (Box 50)
  - Due, Linnea A. (Box 211)
  - Duncan, Robert L. "James Hall Roberts" (Box 50)
  - Duncan, Robert L. (Box 51)
  - Durban, Pam (Box 211)
  - Durbin, Charles (Box 211)
  - Durbin,Charles (Box 52)
  - Durham, Michael (Box 52)
  - Dywasuk, Colette (Box 211)
  - E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. (Box 52)
  - Dutton, Mary (Box 52)
  - Dwight, Harrison Griswold (Box 52)
  - E - misc. (Box 53)
  - Eades, Joan (Box 211)
  - East, P.D. (Box 53)
  - Eastwood, James (Box 53)
  - Eastwood, James (Box 211)
  - Eckert, Allan W (Box 211)
  - Eckert, Allan W. (Box 53)
  - Eckert, Allan W. (Box 54)
  - Edel, Leon (Box 54)
  - Edmonston, Paul (Box 211)
  - Edwards, Tom (Box 211)
  - Ehle, John (Box 54)
  - Ehrlich, Richard (Box 211)
  - Elias, Sylvia (Box 211)
  - Ellis, Humphry Francis (Box 54)
  - Elman, Richard (Box 211)
  - Elsberry, Terence (Box 211)
  - Elston, Allan Vaughn (Box 54)
  - English, Richard (Box 55)
  - Epps, Archie C. (Box 55)
  - Ernst, Paul (Box 55)
  - Etra, Jan (Box 212)
  - Evain, Elaine "Elaine Evyan" (Box 212)
  - Evans, Elizabeth (Box 212)
  - Evans, Mel (Box 55)
  - F - misc. (Box 55)
  - F - misc. (Box 212)
  - Fackler, John (Box 212)
  - Fadiman, Edwin, Jr. (Box 212)
  - Farmer, Eugene (Box 212)